Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The long-awaited Star Festival had just begun.
This event features the annual rankings of each Magic Knight Squad,
followed by an announcement from the Wizard King regarding which squad earned the most stars.
Kahono and Kiyoto!
Asta had invited his friends from the Underwater Temple to join in on the fun.
The magic from the Queen of Witches restored both Kiyoto's leg and Kahono's voice.
Then, during all the excitement...
Hey, Asta.
I've been meaning to ask you, what do you think about Noelle?
What do I think?
You're pretty great.
I like you a lot, Noelle.
Ah!
Where did that come from?
I swear you get dumber every day!
Ah!
What did I do?
To Asta's surprise, he discovered Yami and Jack the Ripper,
captain of the green praying mantises,
involved in what looked like the beginnings of a bitter showdown.
How could I get yourems like this fase where I'm going from?
Good girl, tried to come out from here.
And when it got through the colors that and auf Te 검ated?
I want the flashlight my eyes to to such elements by knowingly.
Oh
is
I'll take another one, please!
Gather round, everyone!
It's a spectacular song and dance from under the sea!
What a beautiful melody.
He's such a talented dancer.
I'm happy to see the two of them doing the things that they love again.
It's touching.
Not bad, dorks.
Just who do you think you are?
Don't crowd royalty!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I guess I did blow him off.
I wonder where he ended up.
He's such an idiot.
All right, Asta, where did you go?
Would you like a plate?
No, maybe later.
Care to try your luck, miss?
Maybe later.
A snack for a lovely lady?
Later.
Where?
Actually, yeah, now's good.
I have to admit, commoners really know their food.
This is tasty.
Now I just need to figure out where Asta landed.
What's with that big concentration of mana?
Hey, everyone!
Who's hungry?
Yeah, step right up!
Try some of Captain Yami's famous grilled squid,
because Yami makes it yummy!
Don't listen to him!
Ha-ha!
Captain Jack's meat dishes are second to none!
One bite, and they'll send your taste buds
on a one-way trip to culinary paradise!
That's right!
You've never had anything like it!
It's food for the body and the fall!
Come and get it!
Get here!
What's going on out there, kid?
If you don't work on that sales pitch
and bring in some more customers,
you're going to be the one getting grilled!
Right!
I'm on it!
Hey there, mister!
What do you say to some delicious squid?
The price is fair and the flavor is totally incredible!
I squid you not!
Hey, rookies!
If you three don't draw on some business,
I'm going to carve you up next!
Ra-haunter!
All right, now who's hungry?
Come have a taste!
Help me or we'll all be lunch meat.
We're good at home!
Monster Chase, right over here!
Who wants some grilled squid?
It's a nutritious treat straight from the sea!
We're begging you!
A customer!
Okay, he flat out ignored me.
This is only happening because Captain Jack
decided to get competitive with the captain of the Black Bulls.
We can't give this stuff away!
It's so tragic.
Did you say something?
Get it, one!
So delicious!
Look, it's not like they're poisoned!
This stagnant mana!
What are you doing?
You gotta help me out here, Noelle!
What?
Oh, hey.
The Ha-Ha Guy.
Greetings, fair maiden!
I'd prefer it if you didn't call me Ha-Ha Guy.
My name is Seke Brunzatsa!
Yeah, whatever.
I don't care.
Anyway, what are you doing with this Seke person, or whoever he is?
Captain Yami...
And Captain Jack are?
Ke-ke-ke!
I always knew that we'd end up settling the score eventually.
Your concessions stand, or my!
Let's see who can sell the most food!
Get ready!
No one's gonna buy from a freak like you!
Hurl your insults now, because when you lose, I'll flay you alive!
You're the loser here, Stringbean, and that means you're about to be wiping my ass for the rest of eternity!
That'd be terrifying if I had a chance of losing!
Let's put an end to this!
Now!
Sweet!
Yeah!
Really?
That's why we're trying to get all the customers we can.
But neither of us have sold anything!
Come on up and get your grilled violet snake, folks!
Piping hot off the fire!
Sounds good!
I'll take it!
Don't get distracted by other stalls!
Yeah, but they have violet snake!
My rainbow squid is better!
I risked my life in a storm off the coast of Rockway to catch those things with my years of fishing experience!
They're the best squid money can buy!
So don't you dare compare them to those damn purple worms!
Geez, I'm sorry!
If I lose to Jack, it's gonna be all your fault, do you hear me?
Come get some ground squid here!
Caught off the coast of Rockway by the captain and Sullivan!
They're just as good as the pot potatoes from Oz Village!
You trying to ruin my business?
No wonder I haven't had a single sale today!
Squid! Buy some squid!
Oh no, Ashtar!
This kid's friggin' useless.
Mine were just as unhelpful.
Kick it!
You know, this method of competition is a bit too slow, if you ask me.
That's funny, I was just thinking the exact same thing.
So now what?
I say we do something that's a little more our style.
Time to fight to the death!
The death?
Look here!
Let's play major luck!
This way!
Idiots!
Let's change it up!
Your funeral, pal!
Next game!
This is going nowhere.
Kick-Ka!
Come on, fight me!
For real!
Yeah, you don't want me to do that.
Am I supposed to be intimidated?
Look, we're killing the party here.
Let's take this showdown somewhere else.
This is a good time to leave.
I believe.
Osta!
What's wrong with you?
Get a hold of yourself, dorksta!
This is embarrassing!
Noel!
What is it?
Go and hunt down Finro for me.
Hey, this is...
I don't think we'll be bothering anybody all the way out here.
The squid's got me feeling energized, so you better get ready for a beating.
I'm glad you're enjoying that squid, because you're about to be chopped up and filleted as well!
Kick-Ka!
Can I get dragged into this again?
This one's pretty good, too.
Our Captain Jack once cut a whole mountain clean in half like it was nothing!
Sorry, but the Captain of the Black Bulls doesn't stand a chance against defeating him!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Uh, what's the ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
How exciting. I can't wait to see what kind of powerful spells they might show us.
Last chance to walk away, Jackie boy.
Kick here. Thanks for the concern, Yamisaki hero.
But under the circumstances, I think you should be more worried about yourself.
These blades of mine are just aching to rip you to shreds.
So let's go.
Last time we fought, it wasn't a whole lot of fun for me since you were on your last leg and all.
Wait, who'd you say was on their last leg?
You, obviously. Those punks from Eye of the Midnight Sun beat you senseless.
Don't be ridiculous. That was an act.
I was just getting ready to turn the tables on the second you showed up on the scene.
Kick here. Sure you were.
I can see that you're feeling pretty confident,
so cutting you to smithereens is going to be a real treat for me.
Somebody's getting cut. That's for damn sure.
Well, these two are as scary as ever.
Whoa. This is awesome. Their key is through the roof.
Why can't there be any normal Magic Knight captains?
A breathtaking battle is about to begin. Ha-ha!
Again. What's with this guy?
Dark magic.
Dark cloak. Black. Blade.
Can't care. That's not bad.
Severing magic.
Shun-tie.
Did you see that?
Oh, come on. That was nothing.
We all know Captain Yami has way more powerful abilities.
That's our Captain Jack.
Damn, that was dangerous.
He's okay.
That's right. His lightless slash allows him to draw in his opponent's magic attacks.
So that's why Captain Jack couldn't hurt him.
We never doubted you for a second, Captain!
Now we're talking. Both Yami and Jack have such incredible magical prowess.
Why don't you let me show you something?
Okay.
I just happen to have an ace in the hole.
Oh, well then let's see it.
During that underwater temple mission, I awakened a brand new spell.
Now I even scare myself.
Okay, okay. That sounds interesting.
Show me what you've got, then.
Did he say new spell?
No, he wouldn't.
What's all this?
He's gonna use that on him?
This is bad news, Finral. Don't you think he'd better put a stop to it soon?
What? Me?
That spell's too serious for just this.
You're right. Jack is a magic knight, Captain. We can't let Yami hit him with something that deadly.
Yeah, good point.
If one of them goes down, someone will be held responsible.
Besides, the Clover Kingdom's defenses will suffer without them.
And then what'll happen?
Something bad?
What if the Diamond Kingdom army or the Eye of the Midnight Sun decides to attack us?
If you don't stop this now, then it's on your head.
You'd blame me for that?
Oh, your fault! Do something!
This guy's the worst.
You will fix this. It is a royal command.
Oh, you love using that, don't you?
She's right, though.
I have to intervene.
We can't afford to lose one of them.
When he first cast Dimension Slash, I thought the cave would fall in.
If it does...
We're all screwed.
I'm the highest-ranking knight here, so it's up to me.
Hey, I think you'd better stop this right now, Captain Yami!
No!
Sindrel!
Mind your own business!
Talk about being useless.
Indeed, that was utterly shameful.
You're not exactly helping either.
Bring it on!
After you!
Dark magic!
Dark clothes!
Separate magic!
Dimension Slash!
Time-binding magic chronostasis!
I would have liked to see that new spell.
Unfortunately, as Asta and friends so wisely concluded,
we shouldn't allow such harm to befall our Magic Knight captains,
nor should we risk the cave collapsing in on itself from the impact, for that matter.
We'll just save Dimension Slash for another time.
Your Majesty!
Where did you go now?
Oh, hello, Marks.
I've been out observing something interesting.
We're much too busy for fun and games, sir.
We have to prepare for the announcement of the Magic Knight's rankings from the Star Festival this evening.
Oh, is that today?
Would you please try to be reasonable?
Our nation's king is waiting!
You must return at once!
It isn't healthy for you to be so uptight, you know.
Do try to relax more, Marks.
It's because of you!
Well, it would appear that I'm needed elsewhere.
I'm sure we'll meet again soon.
Ah.
Before I take my leave, let's be sure to prevent these two from fighting anymore.
Now, let's see here.
There, that should do the trick.
Dimension Slash!
Splash!
Huh?
Go Dead Sights!
What just happened?
Huh?
Put some pants on, you sicko!
K-Kah!
Back at you!
Hm.
K-Kah!
Man!
I feel pretty stupid now.
Stop making me laugh, Yami!
I think I've lost my urge for slashing.
K-Kah!
So, is it over?
Whew, that's a relief.
Now I won't have to worry about getting blamed for anything.
And you two!
What would you have done if somebody had died?
You idiots!
We all know this guy wouldn't go down that easily.
You're missing the point!
The closer people are, the more they fight.
Just make sure to do it responsibly.
Ha-ha!
Look, your little shtick is getting old.
Hey, this is decent.
Your food isn't half bad either.
Well, I'm glad you think so.
Give me a minute and I'll whip up some dessert for you.
Why are you standing there? Go get the thing!
Yes, Captain.
Watch it learn.
It's so cold!
Wow, that's impressive.
Give it a try.
Thank you.
They fight because they're so close, huh?
Maybe Sekei was right.
Uh, hey, Asta.
Look, if you argue with me once in a while, I guess I don't mean too much.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna go and see what everyone else is up to.
Uh, we might as well call it a draw for the day.
That puts me at 53 wins, no losses, and 34 draws.
I don't think so.
Because by my count, we're at 98 wins, no losses, and one draw from me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I meant to say I've got no losses and 156 wins.
Then I've got 567 wins.
No way!
I can prove it!
If you want to settle the score once and for all, we can do it right now.
I thought you'd never ask.
Bring in shrimp.
Come and get me, musclehead!
Again?
Hurry, Asta, you have to stop them!
Why?
Because you're the only one here.
You're here, aren't you?
I can't, I'm royalty.
Wait a minute, let's all calm down and...
Shut up!
Cut, cut!
See, now there's really no one else!
If you say so.
Here's the thing, Captain Yami.
And Captain Jack, we came to the festival to have a good time, not beat each other up,
so could you maybe just try to get along for today?
Pretty please?
Look, kid.
Don't butt in.
Asta, come back!
Thank you so much!
You've been such a wonderful audience!
Just wait and see!
One day we'll become famous pop stars!
The singing, dancing, magic-using idols!
Kahono!
And Kioto!
We look forward to your support!
And making a lot of money!
A whole lot!
Hey, Kioto!
Hey, Kahono!
Asta?
There you are, Finral.
I was starting to wonder what you were up to.
Collecting rejections, I assume?
I mean, that is a thing that happened.
But there's a lot more to the story, too.
Oh, is that so?
Yeah, I'm exhausted.
Oh, loosen up!
The Star Festival is just getting started!
No!
Thanks!
Come on!
Drink up, sweetie!
Cheers!
Might as well.
Hmm?
I know what happens to Captain Yami,
this is so many more than you do as your spatial magic.
That must have been...
Ah!
Are you okay, son?
Jeez, Captain Yami, did you have to throw me that far?
You survived that?
Wow, talk about resilient.
Where the heck am I now?
I gotta hurry and get back to the others.
She's so beautiful.
Look at her.
She must come from money.
Hey, why don't you go talk to her?
No way, I can't!
They're right, she is pretty.
I bet you Finral would go crazy.
Wait a second.
I think I've seen her before.
Let's do it.
I'll make it true, my soul
My days
この世界に響かせいこう
駆け抜けた日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
曲がりくなった道さの暗が
輝ける明日を映すメロディー
but you're not going to cheat and use magic
like that one chef did before, are you?
What?
Just watch
First pull out the guts and cut slits into it
Real directions!
Yeah
Then you season it with salt, sugar, mirin, and ginger
Okay
Then grill it
Normal cooking!
And done
Yummy!
There you have it
Grilled delicious squid that anyone can make
No joke this time
Festivals are great!
Girls are way more in the mood to be flirted with here
I swear this is going to be my shot
Black Clover page 69
The Briar Maiden's melancholy
Whoa!
Captain Charlotte's got makeup on!
She's even hotter than normal!
We'll do that
You got lips
It, Be items
ichaam
Pa
iku
It, Be
Right
awan
IT,"!
お